A Guide to the Virginia Auditor of Public Accounts (1776-1928) Expenses and Warrants of the Restored Government of Virginia, 1863-1864
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Virginia Auditor of Public Accounts (1776-1928) Expenses and Warrants of the Restored Government of Virginia, 1863-1864
The Library of Virginia
44187
0.45 cu. ft. (1 box)
Virginia. Auditor of Public Accounts (1776-1928)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
No acquisition information available.
Historical Information
During the Civil War both the state government and the pro-Union Restored Government of Virginia, which was based first in Wheeling and then in Alexandria, had auditors of public accounts.
Scope and Content
This collection contains records concerning the funding of the Restored Government of Virginia's agencies (expenses of the courts and General Assembly), the pay of its officers and employees (salaries of judges, commonwealth attorneys, civil employees), and the collection of revenues. Also included are warrants for the Constitutional Convention held in Alexandria in 1864, and various contingent funds.
Contents List
- Salaries of Judges and Attorney of Commonwealth, 1863-1864 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Expenses of Election, 1863-1864 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Janitor to the Executive, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Expenses of the Civil Contingent Fund, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Coroners Inquest, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Special Contingent Appropriations, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Delinquent Tax, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Special Appropriation - D. Turner, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Vaccine Agent, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Salary of the Adjutant General, 1863-1864 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Contingent Expenses, Adjutant General Office, 1863-1864 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- I.W. Webb, Check, North Western Bank, Wheeling, 1863-1864 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Appropriation to West Virginia, 1863-1864 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Treasurers Clerk, 1863-1864 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Check, M and M Bank, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Expenses of the Constitutional Convention, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Salaries of the Officers of Civil Government, 1863-1864 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Commissioner of the Revenue, 1863-1864 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Contingent Expenses of Auditors, Secty and Treasurers Office, 1863-1864 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Expenses of Convicts in Jail, 1863-1864 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Expenses of the General Assembly, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Expenses of the Courts of the Commonwealth, 1863-1864 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Audtiors Clerk, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 23)